Guide to the Giant Food Stores Advertising Collection, 1951-2001 RL.00447
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Microfilm Series, 1967-1993, 393 Reels
  - Microfilm: Advertisements
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1976 Dec.-1977 Jan. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-177)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1977 Feb.-Mar. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-178)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1977 Apr.-May (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-179)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1977 June-July (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-180)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1977 Aug.-Sept. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-181)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1977 Oct.-Nov. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-182)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1977 Dec. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-183)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1978 Jan.-Apr. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-184)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1978 May-July (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-185)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1978 Aug.-Nov. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-186)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1978 Dec.-1979 Feb. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-187)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1979 Mar.-May (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-188)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1967 Jan.-June (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-189)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1967 July-Dec. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-190)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1968 Jan.-Dec. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-191)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1969 Jan.-Feb. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-192)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1969 Mar.-May 8 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-193)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1969 May 8-July 11 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-194)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1969 July 14-Sept. 22 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-195)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1969 Sept. 24-Dec. 1 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-196)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1969 Dec. 4-1970 Jan. 30 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-197)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1970 Feb. 2-May 1 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-198)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1970 May 4-July (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-199)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1970 Aug.-Oct. 1 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-200)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1970 Oct. 5-Dec. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-201)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1971 Jan.-Feb. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-202)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1971 Mar.-Apr. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-203)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1971 May-July 1 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-204)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1971 July 6-Oct. 1 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-205)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1971 Oct. 4-Dec. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-206)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1972 Jan.-Mar. 2 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-207)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1972 Mar. 6-Apr. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-208)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1972 May-July 28 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-209)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1972 July 30-Sept. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-210)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1972 Oct.-Dec. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-211)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1973 Jan.-Mar. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-212)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1973 Apr.-June (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-213)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1973 July-Sept. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-214)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1973 Oct.-Dec. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-215)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1974 Jan.-Mar. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-216)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1974 Apr.-June (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-217)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1974 July-Sept. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-218)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1974 Oct.-Dec. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-219)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1975 Jan.-Mar. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-220)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1975 Apr.-June (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-221)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1975 July-Sept. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-222)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1975 Oct.-Dec. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-223)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1976 Jan.-Mar. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-224)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1979 July 9-Aug. 29 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-225)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1979 Aug. 30-Dec. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-226)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant + Competition, 1979 Aug.-Dec. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-227)
    - Washington, D.C.: Post and Star, 1979 July 10-Aug. 29 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-228)
    - Washington, D.C.: Star, 1976 Apr.-July (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-229)
    - Multiple cities: Baltimore News American, Frederick News, Frederick Post, Salisbury Times, 1983 Oct.-Dec. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-230)
    - Multiple cities: Baltimore News American, Frederick News, Frederick Post, 1983 Jan.-June (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-231)
    - Multiple cities: Baltimore Sun, Frederick News, Frederick Post, Fredericksburg Free Lance-Star, 1980 Jan.-June (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-232)
  - Microfilm: Circulars
    - 1968 Mar.-Oct. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-233)
    - 1968 Oct.-1969 Sept. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-234)
    - 1973 July 9-Sept 24 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-235)
    - 1980 May-July (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-236)
    - 1980 Aug.-Oct. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-237)
    - 1980 Nov.-Dec. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-238)
    - 1981 Jan.-Mar. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-239)
    - 1981 Apr.-Sept. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-240)
    - 1981 Oct.-Dec. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-241)
    - 1982 Jan.-Mar. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-242)
    - 1982 Apr.-Sept. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-243)
    - 1982 Oct.-Dec. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-244)
    - 1983 Jan.-Mar. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-245)
    - 1983 Apr.-June (1 of 2) (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-246)
    - 1983 Apr.-June (2 of 2) (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-247)
    - 1983 Oct.-Dec. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-248)
    - 1984 Jan.-Mar. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-249)
    - 1984 Apr.-June (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-250)
    - 1984 July-Sept. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-251)
    - 1984 Oct.-Dec (1 of 2) (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-252)
    - 1984 Oct.-Dec (2 of 2) (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-253)
    - 1985 Jan.-Mar (1 of 2) (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-254)
    - 1985 Jan.-Mar (2 of 2) (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-255)
    - 1985 July-Sept. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-256)
    - 1985 Oct.-Dec. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-257)
    - 1986 Jan.-Feb. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-258)
    - 1986 Mar. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-259)
    - 1986 Apr.-June (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-260)
    - 1986 May-July (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-261)
    - 1986 Aug. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-262)
    - 1986 Sept.-Dec. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-263)
    - 1987 Jan.-Mar. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-264)
    - 1987 Mar.-May (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-265)
    - 1987 June (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-266)
    - 1987 June-July (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-267)
    - 1987 Aug.-Sept. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-268)
    - 1987 Sept.-Nov. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-269)
    - 1987 Nov.-Dec. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-270)
    - 1988 Jan. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-271)
    - 1988 Jan.-Mar. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-272)
    - 1988 Mar.-Apr. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-273)
    - 1988 May-June (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-274)
    - 1988 June-July (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-275)
    - 1988 July-Sept. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-276)
    - 1988 Sept.-Oct. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-277)
    - 1988 Oct.-Nov. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-278)
    - 1988 Nov.-Dec. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-279)
    - 1989 Jan. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-280)
    - 1989 Feb. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-281)
    - 1989 Mar. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-282)
    - 1989 Apr. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-283)
    - 1989 May (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-284)
    - 1989 June (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-285)
    - 1989 July (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-286)
    - 1989 Aug 6-19 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-287)
    - 1989 Aug 20-Sept 9 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-288)
    - 1989 Sept 10-Oct 7 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-289)
    - 1989 Oct 8-29 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-290)
    - 1989 Oct 29-Nov 25 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-291)
    - 1989 Nov 26-Dec 17 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-292)
    - 1989 Dec 18-31 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-293)
    - 1990 Jan 7-28 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-294)
    - 1990 Jan 28-Feb 17 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-295)
    - 1990 Feb 18-Mar 11 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-296)
    - 1990 Mar.-Apr. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-297)
    - 1990 Apr (1 of 2) (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-298)
    - 1990 Apr (2 of 2) (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-299)
    - 1990 May (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-300)
    - 1990 June (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-301)
    - 1990 July (1 of 2) (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-302)
    - 1990 July (2 of 2) (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-303)
    - 1990 Aug. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-304)
    - 1990 Sept (1 of 2) (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-305)
    - 1990 Sept (2 of 2) (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-306)
    - 1990 Oct. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-307)
    - 1990 Nov. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-308)
    - 1990 Dec (1 of 2) (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-309)
    - 1990 Dec (2 of 2) (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-310)
    - 1991 Jan. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-311)
    - 1991 Feb. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-312)
    - 1991 Mar. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-313)
    - 1991 Mar.-Apr. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-314)
    - 1991 Apr.-May (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-315)
    - 1991 May (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-316)
    - 1991 June 2-16 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-317)
    - 1991 June 23-30 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-318)
    - 1991 July 17-21 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-319)
    - 1991 July 28-Aug 11 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-320)
    - 1991 Aug 18-Sept 1 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-321)
    - 1991 Sept 8-15 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-322)
    - 1991 Sept 22-29 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-323)
    - 1991 Oct 6-13 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-324)
    - 1991 Oct 20-27 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-325)
    - 1991 Nov 3-10 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-326)
    - 1991 Nov 17-24 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-327)
    - 1991 Dec 1-8 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-328)
    - 1991 Dec 15-29 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-329)
    - 1992 Jan 5-12 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-330)
    - 1992 Jan 19-26 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-331)
    - 1992 Feb 2-9 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-332)
    - 1992 Feb 16-23 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-333)
    - 1992 Mar 1-8 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-334)
    - 1992 Mar 15-22 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-335)
    - 1992 Mar 29-Apr 5 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-336)
    - 1992 Apr 12-18 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-337)
    - 1992 Apr 19-26 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-338)
    - 1992 May 3-10 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-339)
    - 1992 May 17-25 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-340)
    - 1992 May 26-30 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-341)
    - 1992 May 31-June 6 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-342)
    - 1992 June 7-13 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-343)
    - 1992 June 14-20 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-344)
    - 1992 June 21-27 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-345)
    - 1992 June 28-July 4 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-346)
    - 1992 July 5-11 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-347)
    - 1992 July 12-18 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-348)
    - 1992 July 19-25 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-349)
    - 1992 July 26-31 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-350)
    - 1992 Aug 16-22 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-351)
    - 1992 Aug 23-29 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-352)
    - 1992 Aug 30 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-353)
    - 1992 Sept (1 of 4) (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-354)
    - 1992 Sept (2 of 4) (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-355)
    - 1992 Sept (3 of 4) (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-356)
    - 1992 Sept (4 of 4) (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-357)
    - 1992 Oct 4-10 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-358)
    - 1992 Oct 11-17 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-359)
    - 1992 Oct 18-24 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-360)
    - 1992 Oct 25-31 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-361)
    - 1992 Nov 1-7 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-362)
    - 1992 Nov 8-14 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-363)
    - 1992 Nov 15-21 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-364)
    - 1992 Nov 22-28 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-365)
    - 1992 Nov 29-Dec 5 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-366)
    - 1992 Dec 6-12 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-367)
    - 1992 Dec 13-19 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-368)
    - 1992 Dec 20-26 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-369)
    - 1992 Dec 27-31 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-370)
    - 1993 Jan 3-9 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-371)
    - 1993 Jan 10-16 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-372)
    - 1993 Jan 17-23 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-373)
    - 1993 Jan 24-30 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-374)
    - 1993 Jan 31-Feb 6 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-375)
    - 1993 Feb 7-13 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-376)
    - 1993 Feb 14-20 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-377)
    - 1993 Feb 21-27 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-378)
    - 1993 Feb 28-Mar 6 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-379)
    - 1993 Mar 7-13 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-380)
    - 1993 Mar 14-20 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-381)
    - 1993 Mar 21-27 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-382)
    - 1993 Mar 28-Apr 3 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-383)
    - 1993 Apr 4-10 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-384)
    - 1993 Apr 11-17 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-385)
    - 1993 Apr 18-24 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-386)
    - 1993 Apr 25-May 1 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-387)
    - 1993 May 2-8 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-388)
    - 1993 May 9-15 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-389)
    - 1993 May 16-22 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-390)
    - 1993 May 23-29 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-391)
  - Microfilm: General Merchandise
    - 1967 Jan.-1969 Mar 5 (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-392)
    - 1967 Jan.-1970 Jan. (Box FP17, Reel MF-O-393)
- Scrapbooks Series, 1970-1982, 5 boxes
  Includes eight scrapbooks with fullpage newspaper advertisements, dating from 1970-1982.
  - Advertising Scrapbook, 1970-1973 (Box SB1)
    General fullsize newspaper ads glued or loosely attached to black scrapbook pages. Many feature consumer advocate Esther Peterson, including the following themes:
    Discount pricing, Giant goes discount
    Unit pricing, Goodbye slide rule
    Consumer Bill of Rights
    Recycled paper products
    Giant brand products
    Nutritional labeling, We're making progress
    Beef, You have the right to be informed
    Giant truckers
    Detergents and water pollution
    Welcome Home Mr. President, addressed to President and Mrs. Nixon, 1972 Jun 3
    We love you Melissa, addressed to Olympic swimming champion Melissa Belote, 1973 Sep 15
  - Advertising Scrapbook, 1970-1976 (Box SB1)
    General fullsize newspaper ads, including the following themes:
    Sugar prices
    Immunization
    Beef
    Halloween
  - Advertising Scrapbook, 1972-1978 (Box SB2)
    General fullsize newspaper ads glued on beige scrapbook pages, post-bound. Including the following themes:
    Discount catalogs and catalog showcase
    Giant department stores and store openings in Bowie, Maryland, 1973
    Going out of business ads for Giant department stores, 1978
    Pants Corral
  - Advertising Scrapbook, 1982 (Box SB2)
    Fullsize newspaper ads and quarter-page reprints on black scrapbook pages in vinyl, spiral bound book, documenting Somplace Special, Giant Gourmet in McLean, Virginia.
  - Advertising Scrapbook, 1970-1973 (Box SB3)
    General fullsize newspaper ads on black scrapbook pages in vinyl book, including the following themes:
    Seafood
    Dairy
    Prices and government requested price freeze, 1972 Jan 3
    Heidi Bakery
    Open dating
    Open letter to Washington Redskins football team after a victory over the Cowboys, 1971 Oct 6
    Giant truckers, Driving is a civic duty
  - Advertising Scrapbook, 1973-1978 (Box SB4)
    General fullsize newspaper ads on black scrapbook pages, including the following themes:
    Best wishes to President Nixon on inauguration day, 1973
    Open letter to President Nixon, We are grateful...by bringing the peace we have sought... you have earned our gratitude, 1973 Jan 26
    Earth Week
    Maryland lottery, Why we're selling lottery tickets, 1978
    Meat, Yes we have beef, Mystery at the meat counter
  - Advertising Scrapbook, 1973-1978 (Box SB4)
    Store openings in Alexandria, Baltimore, Frederick
    Pharmacy openings and advertisements
    General seafood ads
    Passover, When the family gathers for a seder, with a list of which stores carry the advertised products
    Store closings, Due to the Maryland Court of Appeals decision on 1973 Jan 2, all Giant Food stores in Maryland will be closed on Sunday
  - Advertising Scrapbook, 1970s (Box SB5)
    General fullsize consumer advocacy newspaper ads and reprints featuring Esther Peterson, on black scrapbook pages in vinyl.
- Oversize Advertisements, 2 boxes
  Window posters, consumer advocacy newspaper ads, and advertising posters promoting Washington area events, healthy eating and nutrition, Giant store programs and reward systems, and other general advertisements.
  - Window posters (Box OA1)
    Including general advertisements and promotions.
    Now shopping has its rewards
    Don't forget to show your card
    Steering you towards saving
    Save money at Giant with checkout coupons
    Take off with US Air
    Virginia Wine Festival
    Buy Now Play Later/Kings Dominion
    Now Selling Kings Dominion
    Orioles Sweepstakes World Series 1987
    50th Anniversary Ice Capades
    2 for 1 at KB Theatre
    Washington Flower Show
  - Poster boards and newspaper ads (Box OA2)
    Includes 29 window posters on board focusing on healthy eating habits. Many advertise the Eater's Almanac or use the logo from Foods for Health pilot nutrition program between Giant Food and the National Institutes of Health. Also includes unbound fullsize consumer advocacy newspaper ads and advertising posters featuring Esther Peterson and Odonna Matthews:
    We support HR 9178 Office of Consumer Representation, 1977 Oct 30
    Eating right is out of sight
    Bicycle safety
    Nutritional labeling
    Meat, Even the White House can't get filet mignon
    Detergents
    Cycle-Giant label of recycled paper products
    Keep food safe from bacteria
    Eat for health-food and cancer risks
  - Locally Grown Produce window posters on board, each featuring a color photograph of a farmer with their name and location. No Giant logo appears on the board. (Oversize-folder 1)
- Printed Materials, 1994-1998, 2 boxes
  Includes an incomplete run of Supermarket News, a weekly trade magazine.
  - Supermarket News, 1994, Volume 44: Issues 16-33; 35-36 (Box PM1)
  - Supermarket News, 1995, Volume 45: Issues 6; 21-27; 29-37; 39-47; 50-51 (Box PM1)
  - Supermarket News, 1996: Volume 46: Issues 1; 3-8; 10-24; 26-28; 30-32 (Box PM1)
  - Supermarket News, 1996: Volume 46: Issues 33-50; 52 (Box PM2)
  - Supermarket News, 1997, Volume 47: Issues 1-2; 5; 7-19; 21-44; 46; 48-49; 51 (Box PM2)
  - Supermarket News, 1998, Volume 48: Issue 1 (Box PM2)